right how do you get Visual Studio
code Visual Studio code Microsoft Visual
Studio code onto your Mac that's what
this video is about it's not hard let's
do it so Brew which you should already
have
installed
install
Visual Studio code we'll let this run
and while this running I want to talk
about it
so what we're doing is we're
connecting
to bruise you know the missing package
manager separate video on that and we're
downloading that and we're going to do
the installation um separate video about
how to get the terminal separate video
about how to colorize your terminal with
group box all those videos exist make
sure you go out and find those if you're
having trouble by the way finding any of
these videos in the order please go to
skill stack and and look at the outline
there and you can see all the videos
will be linked from an outline um which
is much better than a a playlist because
you can go to that and then you can you
can look at everything so there we have
Visual Studio code um the thing to note
about code uh from the command line
whether it's Mac or Windows and and I'll
just do this on both videos is you can
just do which code and that'll tell you
where Visual Studio code is we already
talked about adding opt home brew bin to
your directory uh if you don't know how
to do that and you need to do it for the
first time you can just do opt home
brew uh
Brew SL bin code for your first time if
you've never if you don't know about
that uh it might be by the way it might
be opt user or user local on an Intel
machine this is on the M1 I mean the M3
so any of the arm ones you hit enter and
that is going to open up visual studio
code down here and as soon as you have
that icon down here you can right click
on it and you can add it options uh keep
in
Docker uh keep in Dock and then that way
you can run it there anytime so um
running from the command line is is nice
and I'll do a separate video just about
the things you can do by using the code
command from the command line another
way to start this would have been um
let's go ahead and exit it another way
to start it would have been to do
command space and then type
code Visual Studio code and then type
enter and that would do exactly the same
thing um and you can go ahead and do the
same thing keeping dog so those are the
two ways to get Visual Studio code onto
your Mac using Brew all those other
videos are there see you later